Finding Aid for Office of the Vice President for Research (University of Michigan), Records, 1950-2001
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Central Files
  - Pre-1997
    - National Science Foundation (NSF)
      - Social and Behavioral Science Directorate, 1990 (Box 117)
      - Southeast Michigan Minority Science and Technology Career Access Center Proposal, 1992 (Box 117)
      - State-Industry-University Cooperative Research Center, 1990 (Box 117)
      - Statewide Systemic Initiatives, 1990 (Box 117)
      - Undergraduate Initiatives, 1986-1992 (Box 117)
      - Undergraduate Science, Mathematics, and Engineering Education Initiative, 1991 (Box 117)
    - Natural Resources and the Environment, 1992-1993 (Box 117)
    - Neptun A, 1991-1993 (Box 117)
    - Network for Excellence in Manufacturing (NEM), 1995 (Box 117)
    - Neuroscience Laboratory, 1982-1995 (Box 117)
    - Neuroscience Planning, 1989-1990 (Box 117)
    - Neuroscience Program, 1995 (Box 117)
    - North Ingalls Building Animal Facility, 1995-1996 (Box 117)
    - Oak Ridge Associated Universities, 1995 (Box 117)
    - Occupational Safety and Environmental Health, 1991-1993; 1996 (Box 117)
    - Parke-Davis, 1993; 1996 (Box 117)
    - Patterson Research Institute, 1996 (Box 117)
    - PeopleSoft, 1995-1996 (Box 117)
    - Planning Team on Economic and Industrial Development Activities, 1987-1988 (Box 117)
    - Pond Dynamics and Aquaculture Collaboration, 1996 (Box 117)
    - President's Council of Advisors on Science and Technology (PCAST), 1992; 1995 (Box 117)
    - President's Office, 1992-1993 (Box 117)
    - Presidential Initiative Fund (PIF), 1989-1990 (Box 117)
    - Primary Research Scientist, 1995 (Box 117)
    - Pritzker Foundation, 1995 (Box 117)
    - Process Management Executive Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 117)
    - Program in Evolution and Human Behavior (Box 118)
    - Program in Non-Linear Studies, 1991; 1994-1995 (Box 118)
    - Project for the Integrated Study of Global Change, 1992-1996 (Box 118)
    - Protein Structure and Design Program, 1991-1993 (Box 118)
    - Provost Advisory Committee for Excellence (PACE), 1991 (Box 118)
    - Provost Advisory Group on Education (PAGE), 1995-1996 (Box 118)
    - Repatriation, 1996 (Box 118)
    - Reproductive Science Program (RSP), 1990-1996; 2 folders (Box 118)
    - Research America!, 1993; 1996 (Box 118)
    - Research Computing Advisory Committee, 1995-1996; 2 folders (Box 118)
    - Research Computing Task Force, 1994 (Box 118)
    - Research Directions -- Schools, Colleges and Institutes, 1993-1994 (Box 118)
    - Research Excellence Funds, 1991 (Box 118)
    - Research Incentive Program, 1987 (Box 118)
    - Research Partnership Program, 1991-1995 (Box 118)
    - Research Statistics, 1992-1994 (Box 118)
    - Rivers, Lynn, 1996 (Box 118)
    - Robotics, 1994-1995 (Box 118)
    - School of Art, 1996 (Box 118)
    - School of Business Administration, 1992; 1996 (Box 118)
    - School of Dentistry, 1992 (Box 118)
    - School of Education, 1991-1993 (Box 118)
    - School of Information and Library Studies, Proposal, 1995 (Box 118)
    - School of Music, 1990-1993; 1996 (Box 118)
    - School of Natural Resources and Environment, 1991 (Box 118)
    - School of Nursing, 1991 (Box 118)
    - School of Public Health, 1996 (Box 118)
    - Science and Technology Policy -- Forum on Science in the National Interest, 1994 (Box 118)
    - Science Coalition, 1995-1996 (Box 118)
    - Science Development Council, 1988-1992 (Box 118)
    - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (SACUA), 1992-1994 (Box 119)
    - Senior University Research Scientist Lecture, 1988-1992 (Box 119)
    - Sigma Xi Town Meeting on Allocating Federal Funds, 1996 (Box 119)
    - Signature Authority, 1991 (Box 119)
    - Society of Research Administrators, 1996 (Box 119)
    - Solar Car, 1994-1995 (Box 119)
    - Solition All-Optical Terabit Interchanges & Networks (SATIN) Project, 1994-1995 (Box 119)
    - South Africa Initiative, 1993-1995 (Box 119)
    - Southeast Michigan Science Fair, 1989-1991 (Box 119)
    - SPIN Agreement, 1996 (Box 119)
    - State Universities of Michigan, Presidents Council, 1994 (Box 119)
    - Statistical Consultation and Research, 1991-1992 (Box 119)
    - Summer Research Opportunity Program (SROP), 1990; 1996 (Box 119)
    - Task Force on Costs in Higher Education, 1990 (Box 119)
    - Task Force on Organization of the University, 1996 (Box 119)
    - Teaching Research Ethics Workshop, 1994 (Box 119)
    - Technology Advisory Group, 1995-1996 (Box 119)
    - Technology Management Office, 1991-1996; 2 folders (Box 119)
    - Tissue Engineering Initiative, 1994-1995 (Box 119)
    - Undergraduate Research, 1988-1991; 1994 (Box 119)
    - Undergraduate Research Opportunity Program (UROP), 1993 (Box 119)
    - Unit for Laboratory Animal Medicine (ULAM), 1989-1995 (Box 119)
    - United Auto Workers/Ford/School of Social Work Project, 1990 (Box 119)
    - United Auto Workers/GM/School of Social Work Project, 1989-1990 (Box 119)
    - Universities Research Association, Council of Presidents, 1991; 1995-1996; 2 folders
    - University Committee on International Academic Affairs, 1990-1991 (Box 119)
    - University of Michigan, Federal Agenda, 1994-1995 (Box 119)
    - University of Michigan Policy Statement on the Integrity of Scholarship, 1994 (Box 119)
    - University of Michigan Substance Abuse Research Center (UMSARC), 1994-1996; 2 folders (Box 119)
    - University of Michigan Transportation Research Institute (UMTRI) (Box 120)
      - Director Search, 1987-1989 (Box 120)
      - General, 1991-1996 (Box 120)
    - University Relations Office, 1989-1996 (Box 120)
    - University Research Enterprise: Social Science, Humanities and Arts Perspective, 1989 (Box 120)
    - University Science Alliance, 1995 (Box 120)
    - USAID, 1994 (Box 120)
    - Utah-Russia Institute, 1994-1996 (Box 120)
    - Value-Centered Management
      - Committee on Research Excellence and Value-Centered Management, 1995 (Box 120)
      - General, 1994-1996 (Box 120)
    - Vice President for Government Relations, 1991 (Box 120)
    - Vice Provost for Information Technology, 1992 (Box 120)
    - Vice Provost for Medical Affairs, 1991 (Box 120)
    - Virtual Reality Laboratory, 1994 (Box 120)
    - Volume of Research, 1983-1988 (Box 120)
    - Warner-Lambert/Parke-Davis, 1991-1993 (Box 120)
    - Weinreich Grant Renewal, 1994 (Box 120)
    - Whitaker Foundation, 1992-1996 (Box 120)
    - Women's Health Initiative, 1991-1992 (Box 120)
    - Year of Humanities and Arts (YoHA), 1996 (Box 120)
  - 1997-2003
    (mainly 1997-2000 with some earlier carry over)
    - Ann Arbor Chamber of Commerce, 1999 (Box 121)
    - Ann Arbor, City of, 2000 (Box 121)
    - Aquatic Science, 1997-2000 (Box 121)
    - Architecture and Urban Planning, College of, 1997 (Box 121)
    - Architecture and Urban Planning, College of, 1999 (Box 121)
    - Association of American Universities (AAU), 2000 (Box 121)
    - Atlas Project, 1999-2000 (Box 121)
    - Aviron Revenue Distribution, 1999 (Box 121)
    - Awards
      - Dreyfus/New Faculty, 1997-1998 (Box 121)
      - Dreyfus/Teacher-Scholar, 1996-1997 (Box 121)
      - Dreyfus/Teacher-Scholar, 1999-2000 (Box 121)
      - Faculty Awards, 1997-1999 (Box 121)
      - Faculty Recognition Awards, 1997-1998 (Box 121)
      - Faculty Recognition Awards, 1999-2000 (Box 121)
      - Packard Fellowship, 1997-1999; 3 folders (Box 121)
      - Packard Foundation Interdisciplinary Science Program, 1998; 2000 (Box 121)
      - Pew Scholarship,1996-1999 (Box 121)
      - Tyler Prize for Environmental Achievement, 1999 (Box 121)
      - Ungerleider Award, 1998-2000; 2 folders (Box 121)
    - Bentley Historical Library, 1998 (Box 121)
    - Beta Beta Beta Chapter, 1999 (Box 121)
    - Bi-National Science Foundation, 1998 (Box 121)
    - Biomedical Research, 1998 (Box 121)
    - Biomolecular Recognition, 1997; 1996-1998 (Box 121)
    - Biophysics Research Division (BRD), 1997 (Box 121)
    - Biostation, UM, 1998 (Box 121)
    - Blue Sky (Box 121)
    - Bollinger Advisory Committee "LCB [Lee C. Bollinger] Advisory Committee,", 6/15/1999 (Box 121)
    - Celera Genomics, 1999 (Box 121)
    - Cellular and Molecular Biology Program, 1998 (Box 121)
      (Includes salary information)
    - Center for African and African-American Studies (CAAS) Ford Foundation, 1995-1997 (Box 121)
    - Center for the Education of Women (CEW) Cornerstone, 1998-1999 (Box 121)
    - Center for Great Lakes and Aquatic Studies (CGLAS)
      - Review of Activities, 1997 (Box 121)
      - CGLAS, 1997-1998; 2 folders (Box 121)
    - Center for Human Growth and Development (CHGD)
      - General, 1997 (Box 121)
      - CHGD Recruitment, 1997; 1998 (Box 121)
      - CHGD, 1999 (Box 121)
    - Center for Learning through Community Service (CLCS), 1995-1998; 2 folders (Box 121)
    - (UM) Center for Lesbian Gay Bisexual and Transgender Affairs (LGBT), 1997 (Box 121)
    - Center for Organogenesis, 1997-1998 (Box 121)
    - Center for Research-Based Learning, 1998 (Box 122)
      (Center for Research on Learning and Teaching: CRLT)
    - Center for Research on Teaching and Learning, 1999 (Box 122)
    - Center for Research on the Health Effects of Airborne Particulates and Ozone--Proposal, 1997 (Box 122)
    - Center for Russian and Eastern European Studies,1998-1999 (Box 122)
    - Center for Ultrafast Optical Science, 1997-1998 (Box 122)
    - China Data Center, 1997 (Box 122)
    - Clinical Research Infrastructure Task Force Report, 2000 (Box 122)
    - Collaboratory for Research on Electronic Work (CREW), 1997 (Box 122)
    - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (CIC), 1997-1999; 3 folders (Box 122)
    - Committee to Consider Tobacco Investments, 1999 (Box 122)
    - Community of Science Proposal, 1998-1999 (Box 122)
    - Complex Systems Program, 1997-1999 (Box 122)
      (Includes salary dispute information)
    - Complex Systems Review--Wednesday February26, 1997; 1996-1997 (Box 122)
    - Consortium for International Earth Science Information Network (CIESIN), 1997-1998; 2 folders (Box 122)
    - Consortium of Social Science Associations (COSSA), 1998 (Box 122)
    - Cooperative Institute for Limnology and Ecosystem Research (CILER), 1997-1999 (Box 122)
    - Council on Competitiveness, 1997-1998 (Box 122)
    - Council on Government Relations (COGR), 1997-2000; 2 folders (Box 122)
    - Council on Undergraduate Research Institutions Memo, 1998 (Box 122)
    - Culture and Cognition, 1999 (Box 122)
    - CF Conference, 2000; 1999-2000 (Box 106)
      (Cystic Fibrosis Patent Interferences)
      [CR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2100 ]
    - Director of Defense Research Engineering, Office of, 1998 (Box 122)
    - Dentistry, School of, 2000 (Box 122)
    - Detroit Observatory Restoration Project Manual, 1997 (Box 122)
    - Division of Research Development and Administration (DRDA), 1997 (Box 122)
    - Doris Duke Charitable Foundation Proposal, 2000 (Box 122)
    - Ecole Polytechnique France, 1997-1998 (Box 122)
    - Education, Department of, 1998 (Box 122)
    - Electron Microbeam Analysis Laboratory (EMAL), 1997 (Box 122)
    - Ellison Medical Foundation--Scholarship, 1999 (Box 122)
      (Includes nomination information)
    - Energy, Department of, 1997 (Box 122)
    - Engineering, College of, 1998-2000 (Box 122)
    - Engineering, College of--Advanced Technology Program, 1997 (Box 122)
    - Engineering, College of--Task Force on Technology Transfer and Commercialization Report, March 1999 (Box 122)
    - Engineering Research Center, 1999 (Box 122)
    - Environmental Research Institute of Michigan (ERIM), 1997 (Box 122)
    - John A. Faulkner, Nomination (Professorship), 1999-2000 (Box 122)
    - Federal Policy Groups--Humanities and Arts, 1998-1999 (Box 123)
    - Federal Policy Groups--Research and Education, 1998 (Box 123)
    - Federal Policy Groups--Science, 1998 (Box 123)
    - Federal Policy Working Groups, 1999-2000 (Box 123)
    - Federal Reserve, 1999 (Box 123)
    - Financial Aid Newsletter, 1999-2000 (Box 123)
    - Ford Nuclear Reactor, 1997 (Box 123)
    - Ford / UM Discussion Group, 1997-1999 (Box 123)
    - Fraunhofer Initiative,1997 (Box 123)
    - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA), 1999 (Box 123)
    - Fund for the Improvement of Postsecondary Education (FIPSE), 1999 (Box 123)
    - General Council, Office of, 1997 (Box 123)
    - Geographical Information Systems (GIS) Symposium, 1997 (Box 123)
      (on Global Change)
    - GIS Symposium--Speaker Information, 1997 (Box 123)
    - Geographical Information Systems Committee, 1998-2000 (Box 123)
    - Geosciences Initiative, 2000; 1999-2000 (Box 123)
    - Global Change, 1997-1998 (Box 123)
    - Governor's Innovation Forum, 1998-1999 (Box 123)
    - Graduate Student Tuition, 1997 (Box 123)
    - Grand Haven Aquarium, 1997-1998 (Box 123)
    - H-1B Visas, 1998 (Box 123)
    - Health Professionals Partnership Initiative--Site Visits, 1998 (Box 123)
    - Health Service Research, 1997 (Box 123)
    - Hewlett Foundation, 1998-1999 (Box 123)
    - History of Art Journal (Ars Orientalis), 1998-1999 (Box 123)
    - Howard Hughes Medical Institute, 1999-2000 (Box 123)
    - Hughes Proposal--"Strengthening the Undergraduate Biological Sciences Education Program,", 1997 (Box 123)
    - Human Gene Therapy, 2000 (Box 123)
    - I T Zone/Smart Park, 1999 (Box 123)
    - Imagining America, 1998-1999 (Box 123)
    - Indiana University Poynter Center, 1999 (Box 123)
    - Indirect Costs, 1994; 1997-1998 (Box 123)
    - Industrial Initiatives Steering Committee, 1997 (Box 123)
    - Industrial Initiatives Mackenzie RF1, 1997 (Box 123)
    - Industrial Technology Institute, 1997 (Box 123)
    - Information Technology Entrepreneurship Conference, 1999 (Box 123)
    - Information Technology Policy Committee (ITPC), 1997 (Box 123)
    - Institute for the Humanities, 1999 (Box 123)
    - Institute for Research on Women and Gender (IRWG)
      - Correspondence and Reports, 1996-1997 (Box 123)
      - IRWG--Executive Committee, 1997 (Box 123)
      - IRWG--Grant, Wage, and Salary Information, 1996-1998 (Box 123)
    - Institute for Social Research (ISR), 1997 (Box 124)
    - Institute of Gerontology (IOG), 1997 (Box 124)
    - Institutional Review Board (IRB), 1997-1999 (Box 124)
    - IRB Notebook, Short Summary of Current IRB Issues at U-M, 2000 (Box 124)
    - Integrative Graduate Education and Research Training Program (IGERT) UM Workshop, 1999 (Box 124)
    - IGERT UM Workshop, 2000 (Box 124)
    - Intel Corporation (RFP and Grant), 1997-1998 (Box 124)
    - Intelligent Transportation Systems (ITS), 1997-1998 (Box 124)
    - Interdisciplinary Program Working Group (IDPWG), 1998-2000 (Box 124)
    - Interdisciplinary Research Fund, 1997 (Box 124)
    - Interdisciplinary Working Groups, 1999 (Box 124)
      (Specifically the Working Group on Research)
    - Interior, Department of the, 1999 (Box 124)
    - International Business Machines (IBM), 1998-2000 (Box 124)
    - International Center, 1998 (Box 124)
    - International Institute Self Study, 1998 (Box 124)
    - Internet II, 1998-1999 (Box 124)
    - Jet Propulsion Laboratory, 1999 (Box 124)
    - W.M. Keck Foundation, 1999 (Box 124)
    - Law, School of, 1998-1999 (Box 124)
    - LSA (Literature, Science and the Arts) Science Chairs, 1999 (Box 124)
    - Lucent Technologies Foundation, 1999 (Box 124)
    - Magellan Telescope, 1996-2000 (Box 124)
    - Major Research Instrumentation (MRI) Program, 1999-2000 (Box 124)
    - Management Institute Sponsored Projects Game, 1997 (Box 124)
    - Managing Integrity in Research Conference, 1997-1998 (Box 124)
    - Martin Luther King Day, 1997-1998 (Box 124)
    - Materials Science, 1997-1998 (Box 124)
    - Materials Sciences Initiative, 1999 (Box 124)
    - Media Rights, 1999 (Box 124)
    - Medical School, 1998-1999 (Box 124)
    - Medicinal Chemistry, 2000 (Box 124)
    - MERIT, 1998-1999 (Box 124)
    - MERIT--TIREM, 1999-2000 (Box 124)
    - Michigan Economic Development Corporation, 1999 (Box 124)
    - Michigan Ion Beam Laboratory, 1998-1999 (Box 124)
    - Michigan Public Health Institute, 1996-2000; 3 folders (Box 124)
    - Michigan Sea Grant, 1995-1997 (Box 124)
    - Michigan Technical University, 1999 (Box 124)
    - Michigan Virtual Automotive College, 1997 (Box 124)
    - Middle English Dictionary (MED), 1995-1999 (Box 125)
    - Midwest Center for Airborne Particulate Matter Research, 1998-1999 (Box 125)
    - Millennium Project Sports Planning Team, 1998 (Box 125)
    - Minority Post-Docs, 2000 (Box 125)
    - Muddle in the Middle (OVPR/TMO Conference), 1999 (Box 125)
    - Nanomaterials Research (Medical School), 1998 (Box 125)
    - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA), 1997-2000; 2 folders (Box 125)
    - National Center for Integrated Bioremediation Research and Development (NCIBRD), 1997 (Box 125)
    - National Institute for the Environment, 1994-2000 (Box 125)
    - National Research Council, 1998 (Box 125)
    - National Science Foundation (NSF), 1997-1998; 2 folders (Box 125)
    - NSF--Presidential Awards for Mentoring, 1999 (Box 125)
    - Natural Resources and the Environment, School of, 1997-1998 (Box 125)
    - Neuroimaging, 1997-1999 (Box 125)
    - Neuroscience Executive Committee, 1993-1998 (Box 125)
    - Neuroscience Laboratory, 1997-2000 (Box 125)
    - Neuroscience Program, 1998-1999 (Box 125)
    - News and Information Services, 1998 (Box 125)
    - Nits/Matthews, 1994-1997 (Box 125)
      (Pierre Auger Project)
    - Nobel Prize, 1999 (Box 125)
      (Visit of Nobel Laureate, U-M Emeritus Physics Professor, to Ann Arbor)
    - Nursing, School of, 1999 (Box 125)
    - Oak Ridge National Laboratory, 1999 (Box 125)
    - OMB Circular A-110, 1998 (Box 125)
    - Ohio State Campus Chemical Instrument Center, 1998 (Box 125)
    - Organized Research Units Study, 1998 (Box 125)
    - PSU (Pennsylvania State University) Task Force on Research Administration and Technology Transfer, 1997 (Box 125)
    - Physics Department, 1997 (Box 125)
    - President, Office of the, 1998 (Box 125)
    - President's Council of Advisors on Science and Technology (PCAST), 1999 (Box 125)
    - Process Management Lead Team (PMLT), 1998-1999; 2 folders (Box 125)
    - Provost, 1998 (Box 125)
    - R & D Magazine, 1997 (Box 125)
    - Rackham, 1998 (Box 125)
    - Reproductive Sciences Program, 1997-1998 (Box 125)
    - Research America, 1998-1999; 2 folders (Box 125)
    - Research Club, 1998-1999; 2 folders (Box 125)
    - Research Computing Advisory Committee (RCAC), 1997-1999; 3 folders (Box 125)
    - Research Partnership Program, 1998-1999 (Box 125)
      (Includes award application information)
    - Research Priorities, 1997 (Box 125)
    - Science Coalition, 1997-1999; 2 folders (Box 125)
    - Science Technology Policy, 1998 (Box 125)
    - Social Work, School of, 1998 (Box 125)
    - South Africa Initiatives, Office of, 1997-1999 (Box 125)
    - Spencer Foundation, 1999 (Box 126)
    - Sponsored Research, 2000 (Box 126)
    - State Outreach, 1998 (Box 126)
    - Summer History Institutes, 1997 (Box 126)
    - Technology Management Office (TMO), 1997-1998; 2 folders (Box 126)
    - Technology Transfer Retreat--Minutes, August 27, 1999 (Box 126)
    - Technology Transfer Retreat--Notebook Handout to Attendees, August 27, 1999 (Box 126)
    - Technology Transfer Retreat--Fenocketti, Leon, Ph.D., 1999 (Box 126)
    - Undergraduate Education--UROP/WISE, Living Learning, 1998-2000 (Box 126)
    - Undergraduate Research Opportunity Project (UROP), 1996-2000; 4 folders (Box 126)
    - UROP--URC American Association for Higher Education Presentation, 1998 (Box 126)
    - Undergraduate Research--RAIRE Website, 2001; 3 folders (Box 126)
    - Unit for Laboratory Animal Medicine (ULAM), 1997-1998 (Box 126)
    - Universities Research Association Council of Presidents, 1995-2000; 2 folders (Box 126)
    - University of Michigan Endowment Fund, 1999 (Box 126)
    - University of Michigan Greats
      - U-M Greats, 1999-2000 (Box 126)
      - Shannon, Claude, January 1999 (Box 126)
      - Correa, Charles, February 1999 (Box 126)
      - Norman, Jesse, March 1999 (Box 126)
      - Kearse, Amalya, April 1999 (Box 126)
      - Ting, Samuel, May1999 (Box 126)
      - Kahn, Robert, June 1999 (Box 126)
      - Nirenberg, Marshall W., July 1999 (Box 126)
      - Turnley Brothers, September 1999 (Box 126)
      - Blight, James, October 1999 (Box 126)
      - Uhlenbeck, Karen, November /December 1999 (Box 126)
    - University of Michigan Substance Abuse Research Center (UMSARC), 1997-1998 (Box 127)
    - University of Michigan Transportation Research Institute (UMTRI), 1997-1999 (Box 127)
    - University of Otago, 1999 (Box 127)
    - Value Centered Management (VCM), 1997 (Box 127)
    - Veterans Affairs Hospital, 1999 (Box 127)
    - Vice President and Chief Financial Officer, 1997 (Box 127)
    - Vice President for Research, Office of (OVPR) Advisory Board, 2000 (Box 127)
    - OVPR Regents' Presentation, December, 1998 (Box 127)
    - OVPR Regents Reports, May1999-December 2000 (Box 127)
    - Vice President for Student Affairs, Office of, 1997 (Box 127)
    - Virtual Reality Laboratory (VRL), 1997 (Box 127)
    - Women's Studies Program, 1997 (Box 127)
  - 1951-2005, 1995-2005
    - Abraham, Spencer, 1998-2001 (Box 180)
      [ER RESTRICTED until July 1, 2029 ]
    - Advisory Committee on Human Radiation Experiments (ACHRE)
      - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 180)
      - Interim Report
        - October 14, 1994 (Box 180)
        - October 21, 1994 (Box 180)
    - Affymetrix, 2002 (Box 180)
    - Alliance for Science and Technology Research in America, 2001 (Box 180)
    - Altarum Institute
      - General, 2002-2004; 2 folders (Box 180)
      - Compensation Committee Meeting, September 23, 2002 (Box 180)
      - Meeting with President Coleman, January 15, 2003 (Box 180)
      - Space Physics Research Laboratory, no date (Box 180)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences (AAAS), 1998-2001 (Box 180)
    - Angels House Dinner Photographs, no date (Box 180)
    - Ann Arbor Chamber of Commerce
      - Board of Directors Meeting Agendas, January 2003-November 2004 (Box 180)
      - Finance Committee Meeting Agendas, December 2001-October 2003 (Box 180)
    - Ann Arbor Stromal (former Hambrecht and Quist-Emerson), 1989-1990 (Box 180)
    - Anthropology, Museum of: University of Ouagadougou (Burkina Faso) Agreement, 2001 (Box 180)
    - Arab American Center, 2003-2004 (Box 180)
    - Arab American National Museum (AANM), 2005 (Box 180)
    - Architecture and Urban Planning, 2001 (Box 180)
    - Army University, 2000 (Box 180)
    - Art and Design, 2000 (Box 180)
    - Arts of Citizenship (AoC) Program
      - General
        - 1999 (Box 180)
        - 2000 (Box 180)
        - 2001 (Box 180)
      - Executive Committee, 2000 (Box 180)
      - External Review, February 2001 (Box 180)
      - Grant Proposal with Ann Arbor Public Schools, 2001 (Box 180)
      - Project: Developing a Framework to Respond to Media Portrayals: Flint, MI, 2005 (Box 180)
      - Self-Study for External Review, 2001; 3 folders (Box 180)
    - Association of American Universities (AAU), 2002-2005; 2 folders (Box 181)
    - Assault Crisis Center (ACC) Advisory Committee, 1985-1988; 3 folders (Box 181)
    - Astronomy
      - Association of Universities for Research, 2000 (Box 181)
      - Department, 1994 (Box 181)
    - Audit Plan, 2001-2002 (Box 181)
    - Automotive Research Center, 2001 (Box 181)
    - Barcelona, Michael: Grants, 2001 (Box 107)
      [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2031 ]
    - Biocomplexity in the Environment, 2000 (Box 181)
    - Bioinformatics Program Review, 2003-2004 (Box 181)
    - Biological Research Review Committee (BRRC), 2000 (Box 181)
    - Biomaterials Center, 2000 (Box 181)